(Howard:)Let her rip.
(Scene:)- Hi.
- Hey, check it out.
(Leonard:)It's just corn starch and water.
(Sheldon:)They make up a non-Newtonian fluid
which is liquid...
(Sheldon:)...but solid under the percussive action
of the speaker.
(Howard:)That's what makes it get all funky.
(Penny:)Yeah, okay.
(Penny:)Listen, I need to talk to Sheldon.
(Howard(after Raj whispers in his ear):)No, that's what she said, Sheldon.
Okay, I bought the game and I've been
exploring the Island of Tortage.
I can't figure how to pass the guard.
- Do you have the enchanted sword?
- I have a bronze dagger.
You can't slay the guard with a dagger.
(Sheldon:)Lord, it's like the car key
in your apartment door all over again.